Priyanka Bhatnagar

Finance and Data Analyst

CONTACT

ca.priyanka.bh@gmail.com

Sydney, NSW

in https://www.linkedin.co m/in/priyankabhatnagar-87575235/

SKILLS

SQL: MySQL, Postgres, Google

Big Query, sqlite.

Python

Tableau

Power BI

Advanced MS Excel

SAP, Oracle, Hyperion

Xero, Tech1, Modlr

EDUCATION

General Assembly

Data Analytics Immersive, Sep 2023.

Google Coursera

Data Analytics, Jun 2023.

Chartered Accountant

ICAI 2008, CA ANZ, 2019.

MBA (Finance)

FMS, India 2008.

Bachelor of Commerce

India.

PROFILE

I am a seasoned Chartered Accountant (CA ANZ, ICAI) and MBA in Finance, holding extensive experience in financial analysis, planning and financial modelling, working across companies like KPMG and McKinsey &Co.

I am also adept at Data interpretation, Data analysis and Data visualization. I have strong stakeholder management skills, I like challenges and enjoy providing solutions

WORK EXPERIENCE

Data Analytics Projects, General Assembly, Coursera

Apr 2023 - Sep 2023

- LendingClub credit risk analysis and predictive modelling using machine learning in Python.
- COVID Data Analysis using Python and visualization in Tableau.
- UK Gender Pay Gap Analysis using SQL.
- Sydney Airbnb investment Analysis using PowerBi.

Commercial Manager, Vet Partners

Sydney

Apr 2022 - Mar 2023

- Led financial planning and analysis, budgeting, and forecasting -including variance analysis.
- Data Analysis and preparation of Data visualizations for reporting to business stakeholders.
- Business partnered with operations, strategy, IT, and finance departments. Interpreted financial results with CFO, Operations Directors and Regional Managers. Provided key financial insights.
- Acquisitions and M&A process -Prepared preliminary valuations, financial due diligence, and acquisition board reports for key stakeholders.

Key Projects and achievements:

- Led the design and implementation of new online forecasting tool,
- Led system and process improvements to enhance the annual budget process, resulting in a significant increase in productivity.
- prepared of budget model for new acquisition clinics.

Priyanka Bhatnagar

Finance and Data Analyst

AWARDS

Employee of the month -

VetPartners

Super Team - KPMG

Above and Beyond Champ -

KPMG

Rising Star - McKinsey,

EXPERTISE

Communication

Stakeholder management

Cooperation & teamwork

Analytical thinking

Time management

Problem Solving

Finance Business Partner, Telstra

Sydney

Oct 2021 - Mar 2022

- Prepared 3-way Financial Forecasting model with cash flow forecasting for next 10 years.
- Prepared and automated complex revenue model for monthly revenue reporting.
- Updated technical antenna model including data cleaning and wrangling.
- Led monthly management reporting including cash flow, gap analysis and key insights.
- Business partnered with operations stakeholders. Leveraged data-driven insights to optimize messaging across multiple channels. Leveraged datadriven insights to optimize messaging for commercial and operational decision making.

Senior Financial Analyst, Hexagon PPM

Sydney Apr 2021 –

Apr 2021 - Sep 2021

- Worked closely with the key stakeholders, prepared KPI and financial reporting.
- Consolidated subsidiaries' monthly revenue and prepared OPEX forecasts.
- Developed new Dashboards and Revenue Recognition templates through Power BI.
- Business partnered with region heads. Adapted swiftly to evolving demands and exceeded stakeholder expectations with exceptional deliverables via deep dive financial analysis.
- Prepared annual budgets and rolling forecasts.

Senior Financial Analyst, Worley

Sydney July 2017 – Jan 2021

- Managed Prepared management reports and financial analysis using Hyperion business tool.
- Prepared budgets, rolling forecasts, segment reports and investor pack for the half year and fiscal year end.
- Consolidated and analyzed Group results, KPI reports and overhead analysis.
- Prepared half yearly and annual investor presentation and analysis.

Key Projects and achievements:

Priyanka Bhatnagar

Finance and Data Analyst

INTERESTS

Swimming

Reading books

Travelling and Photography

Baking

- Prepared order to cash cycle document by defining standard operations definitions. This led achieving the application of consistent management accounting practices across locations.
- Compiled the annual Global ENR (Engineering News Records) survey, which ranks leading energy companies in ENR magazine. This resulted in the company achieving a top 10 rank in the news listing.

Assistant Manager, KPMG India

April 2012 - April 2017

- Prepared Prepared IFRS accounting, budgets, and forecasts.
- Created financial models for the business and prepared analytical insights for senior stakeholders.
- Led a Special project with the Global leadership team under the COO's office, by Implementing strong finance processes for the treasury team.

Key Projects and achievements:

- MIS redesign Worked with the leadership team under the COO's office on restructuring & implementation of MIS for each function, and at the consolidated level.
- Worked on Forecasting Automation tool, thought process, testing & implementation.
- Initiated & implemented invoice automation project on oracle project module, to handle invoicing volumes.
- Automation of the MIS & invoicing process for UK business.
- Led data sanitization & migration to oracle R12.
- Led testing & implementation of automated MIS dashboard from GL.

Accounting Analyst, McKinsey & Company India

Jan 2011 - Apr 2012

- Prepared IFRS accounting, budgets, and forecasts.
- Created financial models for the business and prepared analytical insights for senior stakeholders.
- Led a Special project with the Global leadership team under the COO's office, by Implementing strong finance processes for the treasury team.

Assistant Manager, DCM Sriram Ltd. India

Jul 2008 - Jan 2011

- · Performed statutory and internal audits.
- Prepared consolidated financial statements, IFRS compliance and reports as per companies act.
- · Prepared annual budget and forecasts.
- Performed GL reconciliations, variance analysis of balance sheet and profit & loss Account.